[
  {
    "question": "Q1. What is the object in the image?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Brain",
      "b": "Heart",
      "c": "Liver",
      "d": "Lungs"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q2. What is the primary function of the heart?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Pumping lymph",
      "b": "Storing urine",
      "c": "Pumping blood",
      "d": "Producing hormones"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q3. How many chambers does the heart have?",
    "options": {
      "a": "2",
      "b": "3",
      "c": "4",
      "d": "5"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q4. What are the upper chambers of the heart called?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Atria",
      "b": "Ventricles",
      "c": "Valves",
      "d": "Arteries"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q5. What is the function of the left atrium?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Receives deoxygenated blood from the body",
      "b": "Pumps oxygenated blood to the lungs",
      "c": "Receives oxygenated blood from the lungs",
      "d": "Pumps deoxygenated blood to the rest of the body"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q6. Which valve is located between the left ventricle and the aorta?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Tricuspid Valve",
      "b": "Pulmonary Valve",
      "c": "Mitral Valve",
      "d": "Aortic Valve"
    },
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q7. What is the main blood vessel bringing oxygen-rich blood from the lungs to the heart?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Superior Vena Cava",
      "b": "Pulmonary Artery",
      "c": "Pulmonary Vein",
      "d": "Aorta"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q8. What is one of the key functions facilitated by the heart?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Digestion",
      "b": "Waste removal",
      "c": "Vision",
      "d": "Hearing"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q9. How can one maintain heart health?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Regular exercise",
      "b": "Smoking",
      "c": "Unbalanced diet",
      "d": "Both a and b"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Q10. What is the size of the human heart?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Size of a hand",
      "b": "Size of a fist",
      "c": "Size of a thumb",
      "d": "Size of a finger"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  }
]